Prey you will make it out alive!
Beneath the Surface is a fantasy, horror, thriller
film directed by Scott Chambers.
A young woman survives a great white shark attack, whilst on a family boating
vacation, however soon realizes the nightmare is far from over.
Those around her can not be trusted, and she must face her
demons, if she is to step back in the water.
Dr. Fran, played by Nicola Wright.
Vicky, played by Stephanie Lodge.
Lexy McKenna, played by Georgie Banks.
DC Du Plessis, played by Julia Quayle.
Amy, played by Beatrice Fletcher.
Chloe, played by Annie Knox.
Beneath the Surface (French: Le Lac des hommes, lit.
'The Lake of Men') is a Canadian documentary film, directed by
Marie-Geneviève Chabot and released in 2021.
An exploration of modern masculinity, the film centres on Laurent Sirois, a man who is on a fishing trip with his sons Jean-Pierre, Stéphane and Jérôme, who
are all dealing with their complicated relationship after his separation and divorce from their mother largely removed him from their childhood.
The film premiered at the 2021 Rendez-vous Québec Cinéma.
It was later screened at the 2022 Canadian Film Festival, where Chabot won the DGC Ontario
award for best director, and at the 2022 Festival de films d’auteurs de Val-Morin.
It went into commercial release in June 2022.
The film explores themes of vacation, summer vacation, shark,
young girls gone dead, young girl not safe.
The tone is mind_bending and dark and emotional.